♪ ♪
♪ YOU MEAN I'VE BEEN DANCIN'
ON THE FLOOR DARLIN' ♪
♪ AND I FEEL LIKE
I NEED SOME MORE ♪
♪ AND I FEEL YOUR
BODY CLOSE TO MINE ♪
♪ AND I MOVE ON LOVE,
IT'S ABOUT THAT TIME ♪
♪ MAKE ME FEEL MIGHTY REAL ♪
♪ ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME FEEL MIGHTY REAL ♪
♪ WHEN WE GET HOME DARLIN' ♪
♪ AND IT'S NICE AND DARK ♪
♪ AND THE MUSIC'S IN VIENNA ♪
♪ STILL YOU'RE HOT AND
YOU KISS ME BACK AND IT ♪
♪ FEELS REAL GOOD AND
I KNOW YOU LOVE ME ♪
♪ LIKE YOU SHOULD ♪
♪ ♪
♪ OH YOU MAKE ME
FEEL MIGHTY REAL ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME FEEL MIGHTY REAL ♪
♪ MAKE ME FEEL MIGHTY REAL ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I FEEL REAL ♪
♪ REAL, REAL ♪
♪ I FEEL REAL, WOO! ♪
♪ ♪
♪ WOO! ♪
♪ I FEEL REAL ♪
♪ REAL REAL ♪
♪ I REAL REAL ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME FEEL MIGHTY REAL ♪
♪ ♪
♪ OH, YOU MAKE ME
FEEL MIGHTY REAL ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME FEEL MIGHTY REAL ♪
♪ OH, I FEEL REAL,
WHEN YOU TOUCH ME ♪
♪ I FEEL REAL,
WHEN YOU KISS ME ♪
♪ I FEEL REAL, WHEN
YOU TOUCH ME ♪
♪ I FEEL REAL,
WHEN YOU HOLD ME ♪
♪ REAL ♪